const biologySeed = [
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What is the phospholipid bilayer with embedded protiens that surrounds every cell?',
    correctAnswer: 'Cell membrane',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Cell wall',
        2: 'Cholesterol',
        3: 'Osmosis'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What are the organelles that transcribe and translate DNA into proteins in every cell?',
    correctAnswer: 'Ribosomes',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Lysosomes',
        2: 'Mitochondria',
        3: 'Vesicles'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What is the rigid structure of mostly cellulose outside of the phospholipid bilayer surrounding plant cells?',
    correctAnswer: 'Cell Wall',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Cell membrane',
        2: 'Cholesterol',
        3: 'Osmosis'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'Known as the powerhouse of the cell, this organelle is where cellular respiration takes place in Eukaryotes?',
    correctAnswer: 'Mitochondria',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Ribosomes',
        2: 'Golgi Apparatus',
        3: 'Endoplasmic Reticulum'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What is the term for pluripontent cells that can self replicate or differentiate to form all different types of cells',
    correctAnswer: 'Stem Cells',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Somatic Cells',
        2: 'Gametes',
        3: 'Prokaryotes'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What organelle packages products in vesicles for transport or storage?',
    correctAnswer: 'Golgi Apparatus',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Endoplasmic Reticulum',
        2: 'Ribosomes',
        3: 'Nucleus'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What organelle contains the DNA in Eukaryotic cells?',
    correctAnswer: 'Nucleus',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Cell membrane',
        2: 'Endoplasmic reticulum',
        3: 'Hard Drive'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What is the process by which plantss convert sunlight into glucose?',
    correctAnswer: 'Photosynthesis',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Cellular Respiration',
        2: 'Fermentation',
        3: 'Osmosis'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What is the process by which organisms convert glucose into ATP?',
    correctAnswer: 'Cellular Respiration',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Photosynthesis',
        2: 'Fermentation',
        3: 'Osmosis'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What is the term for a fertilized egg that is a single cell that will give rise to an entire organism?',
    correctAnswer: 'Zygote',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Gamete',
        2: 'Prokaryote',
        3: 'Sex Cell'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What is the process by which somatic cells duplicate themselves?',
    correctAnswer: 'Mitosis',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Meosis',
        2: 'Cloning',
        3: 'Differentiaiton'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What is the process by which a diploid cell creates 4 haploid cells in preparation for sexual reproduction?',
    correctAnswer: 'Meiosis',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Mitosis',
        2: 'Gametification',
        3: 'Apoptosis'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What is the organelle in which sunlight excites pigments in the first steps of Photosynthesis?',
    correctAnswer: 'Chloroplast',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Mitochondria',
        2: 'Ribosome',
        3: 'Cell Wall'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What has the reactants Oxygen and Glucose and the products Carbon Dioxide, Water, and ATP?',
    correctAnswer: 'Cellular Respiration',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Photosynthesis',
        2: 'Fermentation',
        3: 'Osmosis'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What has the reactants Water, Carbon Dioxide, and Sunlight and the products Glucose and Oxygen',
    correctAnswer: 'Photosynthesis',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Cellular Respiration',
        2: 'Fermentation',
        3: 'Osmosis'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What kind of macromolecules are enzymes?',
    correctAnswer: 'Proteins',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Carbohydrates',
        2: 'Lipids',
        3: 'Good ones'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What kind of macromolecules are broken down for quick energy and made of carbon, hydrogen, and oxygen?',
    correctAnswer: 'Carbohydrates',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Lipids',
        2: 'Proteins',
        3: 'Steroids'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What kind of macromolecules are hydrophobic and used for long term energy storage?',
    correctAnswer: 'Lipids',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Carbohydrates',
        2: 'Proteins',
        3: 'Batteries'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What process has light dependent reactions and light independent reactions?',
    correctAnswer: 'Photosyntesis',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Cellular Respiration',
        2: 'Dependent Variables',
        3: 'Biomedical Assay'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What allows large molecules such as glucose to pass through cell membranes',
    correctAnswer: 'Protein Channels',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Osmosis',
        2: 'Diffusion',
        3: 'Endoplasmic Reticulum'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What is the process by which small molecules such as oxygen and carbon dioxide cross the cell membrane down their concentration gradient?',
    correctAnswer: 'Diffusion',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Protein Channels',
        2: 'Osmosis',
        3: 'Windows'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What Process includes the steps Glycolysis, Krebs Cycle, and the Electron Transport Chain?',
    correctAnswer: 'Cellular Respiration',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Photosyntheis',
        2: 'Fermentation',
        3: 'Light Dependent Reactions'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What is the name for the diffusion of WATER accross a cell membrane?',
    correctAnswer: 'Osmosis',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Diffusion',
        2: 'Aquaducts',
        3: 'Thrist-trapping'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What are the inputs to cellular respiration?',
    correctAnswer: 'Glucose and Oxygen',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Shovels and Rope',
        2: 'Carbon Dioxide and Sucrose',
        3: 'HDMI and USB'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What are the outputs of cellular respiration?',
    correctAnswer: 'Water, Carbon Dioxide, and ATP',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Water and Sunlight',
        2: 'Proteins',
        3: 'Blood, sweat, and tears'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What are the inputs to Photosynthesis?',
    correctAnswer: 'Sunlight, water, and carbon dioxide',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Chlorophorm',
        2: 'Choloroplasts',
        3: 'Oxygen and Water'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What are the outputs of Photosynthesis',
    correctAnswer: 'Glucose and Oxygen',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Energy and Carbon Dioxide',
        2: 'Proteins and Lipids',
        3: 'Chloroplasts'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What will happen to a cell if it is placed in an isotonic solution?',
    correctAnswer: 'It will stay the same size',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'It will grow',
        2: 'It will shrienk',
        3: 'It will die'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'Which organelle is found in plant cells but not in animal cells?',
    correctAnswer: 'Chloroplast',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Nucleus',
        2: 'Ribosome',
        3: 'Mitochondria'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'Which organelle is found in plant cells but not in animal cells?',
    correctAnswer: 'Cell wall',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Cell Membrane',
        2: 'Ribosome',
        3: 'Mitochondria'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b7dcd6b86a544c3a50a",
    question: 'What is the medical term for a muscle cell also known as a muscle fiber?',
    correctAnswer: 'Myocyte',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Oocyte',
        2: 'Neuron',
        3: 'Steriod'
      }]
  },
]

module.exports = biologySeed